After business objectives had been set and contracts have been signed,
在订立业务目标和签订合同之后
it's imperative to find ways to make sure that
必须找到方法确保
your company is diligent about meeting its SLA goals.
您的公司正在努力实现其 SLA 目标
When it comes to infrequent events,
当事件发生时
such as disaster recovery failovers,
比如灾难恢复的仙女
it can be tempting to deprioritize this work.
就会被引诱去剥夺这项工作
You must be very cautious and make sure that you're spending
一定要很谨慎 一定要花钱
the appropriate time and resources to make sure you maintain these capabilities.
确保您保持这些功能的适当时间和资源
Depending on your industry,
根据您的行业
your company may be more or less comfortable with
你的公司可能会对
taking the time and resources to prepare for these types of events.
花费时间和资源准备这些类型的事件
If you work for an industry that is government regulated,
如果你为一个政府监管的行业工作
this is probably a fairly common thing within your company and within your industry.
这可能是公司内部和您的行业内相当常见的事情
If you work at a company that is not government regulated,
如果你在一个不受政府监管的公司工作
your company may be less familiar with taking
你的公司可能不太熟悉
the time and the resources to follow through on these procedures.
这些程序的时间和资源
But it's still imperative to meet
但必须满足
your SLAs and the commitments you've made to your customers.
您的 SLA 以及您对客户所作的承诺